("This Love" by Maroon 5)
♪ I was so high,
I did not recognize ♪
♪ The fire burning in her eyes ♪
♪ The chaos that
controlled my mind ♪
♪ Whispered goodbye as
she got on a plane ♪
♪ Never to return again ♪
♪ But always in my heart ♪
(Oh)
♪ This love has ♪
♪ Taken its toll on me ♪
♪ She said goodbye ♪
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ And her heart is ♪
♪ Breaking in front of me ♪
♪ And I have no choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't say
goodbye anymore
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I tried my best ♪
♪ To feed her appetite ♪
♪ Keep her coming every night
So hard to keep her satisfied ♪
♪ Oh, kept playing love
like it was just a game ♪
♪ Pretending to feel the same ♪
♪ Then turn around
and leave again ♪
♪ But, oh ♪
♪ This love has ♪
♪ Taken its toll on me ♪
♪ She said goodbye ♪
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ And her heart is ♪
♪ Breaking in front of me ♪
♪ And I have no choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't say
goodbye anymore
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I'll fix these broken things ♪
♪ Repair your broken wings ♪
♪ And make sure everything's ♪
♪ Alright
(It's alright, it's alright) ♪
♪ My pressure on your hips ♪
♪ Sinking my fingertips ♪
♪ Every inch of you ♪
♪ 'Cause I know that's
what you want me to do ♪
♪ This love has ♪
♪ Taken its toll on me ♪
♪ She said goodbye ♪
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ Her heart is ♪
♪ Breaking in front of me ♪
♪ And I have no choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't say
goodbye anymore
♪ This love has ♪
♪ Taken its toll on me ♪
♪ She said goodbye ♪
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ And my heart is ♪
♪ Breaking in front of me ♪
♪ She said goodbye ♪
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ This love has ♪
♪ Taken its toll on me ♪
♪ She said goodbye ♪
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ Her heart is ♪
♪ Breaking in front of me ♪
♪ I have no choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't say
goodbye anymore ♪